[{"answer": "Nothing for a while. You forget, I'm a man of independent means. Or fairly independent", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " To forget? Don't be so motherly, my friend. I'm not going to crack up", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " To forget? Don't be so motherly, my friend. I'm not going to crack up", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'm having one now", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I got a call from him today. Funny. He dropped out of sight during the war, and I'd heard he'd gone East. I guess he's back.  It's a Mission number", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Could be", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Is she pretty", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " No, not Carlotta. my friend's wife", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I will. You're terribly direct in your questions", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You're not. Merely direct. What were you doing there? At that place", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You shouldn't have brought me here, you know", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You could have looked in my car. Oh, but you didn't know my car, did you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "My name is my friend", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend. Old friends. Acquaintances call me my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "That's a good, strong name. Do your friends call you my friend? Or my friend", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " I shall call you Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend. Old friends. Acquaintances call me my friend", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " No, I wouldn't like that. And after what happened today I should think you could call me my friend. Or even my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Only silence. It's always like this", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No birds live here", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "When you jumped in the bay, you didn't know where you were. You guessed but you didn't know", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Why did you jump", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I don't know. An open grave. I stand by the gravestone looking down into it. And it's my grave", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I know", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Could I ask you a couple of questions", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "My name is my friend, and", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "No, please! I Just want to talk to you", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'm not going to hurt you! I promise! Please", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Oh, I understand, all right. I've been understanding since I was seventeen. And the next step is, as long as you're going to see me tomorrow, why don't you stay the night", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No? Then what", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No? Then what", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "As friends? We'd just see a lot of each other as friends, and you'd", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "my friend, it can't make much difference to you. I just want to see how you'd look and I know it won't be the same, but", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " my friend, you've got to do this for me! Please", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I told you. I have to go back into the past. Once more. For the last time", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend died here", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "We're going up the tower, my friend", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "We're going up the tower", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I made it", "docId": "vertigo.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Look at the scene of the crime. Go on in", "qsentId": 40}]